+801-503-2036

(4)

aubrey\_jones07@hotmail.com



https://aubrey-jones-webdevelopment-portfolio.netlify.app/



https://aubrey-jones-ux-uiportfolio.netlify.app/

Riverton, Utah (1)

# **Aubrey** JONES

UX/UI Designer && Developer

My name is Aubrey Jones and I often daydream, learn, execute, and teach UX/UI design and frontend web development. I am always ready for a challenge that helps customers have a better user experience through the latest technologies in those processes. Feel free to connect.

# **SKILLS**

## **UX & UI Design**

Interviews, User Personas, Affinity Diagrams, Empathy Maps, User Journey Maps, Sketches, Wireframing, Unit Testing, Style Guides, Design Systems, A/B Testing, Prototyping Figma, Adobe XD, Sketch

## **FRONT-END Development**

HTML/CSS, SCSS, Bootstrap, Material UI5 JavaScript, React JS

## **BACK-END Development**

MongoDB, Express.JS, Node.JS

# **EDUCATION**

**Utah Valley University** 2017 - 2021

**Bachelor's Degree** 

Web Design and Development Emphasis in Web and App Development

**DevMountain** 2016 - 2016

Certificate

UX/UI Design

Salt Lake Community College

2011 - 2016

**Associate's Degree** 

**General Studies** 

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### 01. **UX/UI Designer & Developer Freelancer**

December 2020 - Current

As a UX/UI Designer freelancer I create product and graphic designs using some latest technologies such as Figma, Adobe Creative Cloud, Sketch, etc. I love that I get to explore my creative digital design passion at any time of the day and share it with others. I care to see projects through from inception to production and communicate with others as needed.

#### 02. UX/UI Designer Instructional Specialist - Tutor - Grader **2**U

November 2020 - Current

As a UX/UI Designer Instructional Specialist I get to mentor students and guide them throughout the UX/UI design thinking process and front-end web development. I provide written and verbal feedback on presented projects. I showcase a lot of beginning and advanced software demos such as with Figma, FigJam, Adobe XD, Miro, Codepen, GitHub suite, and Visual Studio Code.

#### 03. **UX/UI** Designer **Codafi Technologies**

September 2020 - November 2020

We worked on agile design sprints as a team which included research, definition and ideation, wireframing, prototyping, and testing. We communicated with the clients. We designed and updated their style guides and feature requests with focus on lean UX.

### 04. **UX/UI Designer and Developer Intern The Family Literacy Centers**

May 2018 - December 2020

I worked on design sprints which included research, definition and ideation, wireframing, prototyping, and testing. I redesigned their Algebra 1 program to have a modern layout and updated it to fit HTML5 and CSS requirements.